{
    "subject": "resource/Lujo_Brentano",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Aschaffenburg",
    "human_readable": "Lujo Brentano was born in Aschaffenburg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9559406638145447,
            "question": "Name the city where Lujo Brentano was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9259898662567139,
            "question": "Where was Lujo Brentano born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6278911232948303,
            "question": "What is Lujo Brentano known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.576045572757721,
            "question": "Where did Lujo Brentano work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4796685576438904,
            "question": "Who were some of Lujo Brentano's contemporaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44181281328201294,
            "question": "In what year did Lujo Brentano live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3364497721195221,
            "question": "What was Lujo Brentano's field of study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32273054122924805,
            "question": "Which university did Lujo Brentano attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24574805796146393,
            "question": "What are some of Lujo Brentano's most influential works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24399572610855103,
            "question": "How did Lujo Brentano's work impact later thinkers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lujo Brentano was born in Aschaffenburg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5809_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Lujo Brentano's most influential works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5809_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which university did Lujo Brentano attend?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5809_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Lujo Brentano's field of study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5809_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5809_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5809_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5809_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5809_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5809_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5809_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5809_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5809_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5809_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5809_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can confirm that the triple is correct.\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Lujo Brentano was born in Aschaffenburg, Germany, which supports the statement that Lujo Brentano was born in Aschaffenburg."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}